[Music]
Brother, this is what I need.  Order it right now.
So this is the mini steam iron which
presses clothes with the help of steam.  So
here I have a shirt.  By the way, I have
ordered it online for ₹500.  So first of all you will have to
fill water inside it from here.
Fill water inside it in this manner.
Water fell on my shirt.  Water.
Ok.  So I filled it with water.   Let's
turn it off from here and now let's turn it on.
Look here the indicator has turned on.  Let's
try to erase the creases in its pocket.  So now it has become a little
hot but it has become very lightly hot
brother.  So here I have steamed it,
look at the steamer also brother, the steamer is also
not working properly.  Water is coming out
from inside it.  And just a
minute of this here.  Brother, this effort is not heating up.
Steam kill brother.  What is?  What's the steam now,
brother?  Look at this.  Brother, he threw water in the name of steam.  On
top of this.  Its steamer is also
not working properly.  But no problem.   The
pockets that are on it, the pockets that are on it.
I will try.
I can't abuse for a minute.
No, don't abuse.